Notice of Withdrawal
Flying Circus Team
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Wha—
N-No way...
What?
Y-Y-You're kidding, right?
Kagami-sensei said she
found this on her desk.
Why, Misaki-chan...
Episode Eight:
"I... Can't Fly Anymore."
Misaki-chan!
Misaki-senpai!
How are you at school already?!
Oh, you must've wound up sleep-
deprived after waking up too early!
So that's why you turned in that notice!
Wait, what does sleep deprivation
have to do quitting the team?!
You're not supposed to point
that out yourself, Mashiro-cchi.
Ugh, keep it down. It's too
early in the meowning.
You're not serious, right?
D-D—
Derp pucker.
What?
Your turn. R.
Huh? R-R...
Rururu...
Uh, this is no time to
be playing word chain.
I never expected Asuka
to play the straight man.
Talk to us, Misaki.
What are you thinking?
Come on! Can't you read?!
Well, I got bored with it. And I couldn't
deal with the morning purractice.
We're being serious here, Misaki.
Don't worry your pretty
little heads about me.
How could we not worry?!
Class is gonna start. Get going.
I'll be back!
Misaki-chan's not coming back.
She ran away, eh?
Misaki-senpai!
Where are you? I brought you udon!
In times like this...
Tobisawa Misaki-san of Class 2-C,
please report to the student
counseling room at once.
What the...?
Did Misaki do something bad?
Maybe she quit the team so she wouldn't
get us caught up in the mess?
What are you two doing here?
Didn't you hear Misaki-chan get summoned?
We got worried and rushed here.
Sorry, that was a trap I set.
Seriously?
I can't believe you two
fell for it and she didn't.
So she hasn't shown up?
Misaki-chan!
Why would you tip off the target?
Misaki!
S-Silly me!
Misaki-senpai!
Mashiro-cchi!
A-Are you all right?
Mission failed.
Misaki-chan...
We still have after school!
We'll put Phase Two of the Capture
Misaki-senpai Operation in motion!
Here's the first part of the plan.
As soon as the bell rings,
Asuka-senpai and Madoka-senpai secure
the front and rear exits of the classroom.
Let's stop here for today.
Uh, could you let me through?
O-Oh, sorry about that.
She ran away!
Misaki-chan!
Misaki!
Tobisawa!
Captain?!
I mean, former captain?!
Were you that hurt by my retirement?!
Bro, I'm dead sure that
wasn't the reason why!
Wh-What? She wasn't
following me out the door?
She went up to the roof?
Cleared fur takeoff!
Oh, come on!
Madoka - Sorry! (>_<;) Look up!
Up?
Misaki-senpai!
It's against the rules to take off from
anywhere other than the terminals.
Why am I running away?
Misaki-chan!
Asuka?!
Jeez!
Misaki-chan!
Please wait!
Why are you quitting?
Did something happen?
I want to keep flying with you!
I... can't fly anymore.
Like, I stopped finding it fun, you know?
You should stick to it, though.
You're good enough to go toe-to-toe with
Shindou-san despite only having just started.
And you're gonna take part in
the fall tournament, right?
Better get back to practice, then.
She can't fly anymore?
Yes.
She said she stopped finding it fun.
In that case, let's turn this
team into something she'd enjoy.
Like?
The FC Udon team!
What kind of team would that even be?
A team that eats udon indoors on rainy days.
How about the FC Nukazuke Pickles team, then?
Or the Sleeping-In FC team?
The Game FC team, maybe!
That's just something you'd enjoy.
Leave her alone.
Quit putting so much pressure on her.
Got it.
Well, Misaki can be pretty
hard to reason with.
Besides, she might come back
all by herself eventually.
Right.
Y'know, I was worried you'd quit with her.
I want to get better and better.
Same here.
The former captain's counting on
us to win the fall tournament, too.
Yeah. Time to grind in practice.
As a famous baseball player once said,
it's the baby steps that lead to big results!
Wow, you're a cutting-edge captain! Got it!
You're making her sound like a razor.
Are you talking about my razor-sharp wit?
Let's do our best!
"Stopped finding it fun," huh?
Do people really fall out of
love with something that fast?
And here I was glad the team was
finally getting back on its feet.
But there's no need to force
yourself to keep going.
Whether you pack it up or
not is entirely up to you.
That said...
You can understand how Tobisawa
feels, right, Masaya?
And just what are you makin' for me?
Wait and see.
Huh? We're out.
I wonder if I can still go out and get some.
Here shopping?
Y-Yeah...
My folks went out tonight,
so I came to buy dinner.
Hey...
Why won't you say anything to me?
I guess it doesn't matter that I'm gone, huh?
There are more talented people left on the team.
Stop it. Don't say that.
Sorry, I...
Oh, I know.
L-Let's eat.
This is great!
It's curry made with flyer stock!
Oh...
I made the fukujinzuke and
rakkyo pickles myself, too.
Eat as much as you like, okay?
I will, thank you.
Thanks for dinner.
See you tomorrow, then—
Misaki.
What?
You asked me earlier why I
wouldn't say anything to you.
It's just that I get how you feel.
Because I ran away from FC, too.
I started playing Flying
Circus in grade school.
I was basically invincible for ages,
and I even won the All-Japan.
At first, I was just happy that I could
soar the skies and had so much fun flying.
The Prodigy
Hinata Masaya
But when I got selected to represent
Japan in the World Cup, I got cold feet.
I think people instinctively get scared
once they dedicate themselves to a craft.
We fear failure. We fear losing.
We fear running into
someone better than us.
The moment I started having those feelings,
I stopped finding flying fun.
That's around the time a boy who called
himself a beginner challenged me to a match.
And would you believe it? I lost.
I felt like I'd gone as far as I could—
that it was the end of the line—
and decided to quit FC right then and there.
Actually, I think I just needed
a reason, any reason, to quit.
I wanted to run away from
FC as quickly as possible.
But there's one thing I've
realized since quitting.
It's hard to run away.
Misaki wasn't her usual self today either.
It was as if her mind was somewhere else,
even while eating udon for lunch.
I've never seen her be that
apathetic toward udon before.
Not you, too, Asuka-senpai.
What did she mean, flying
wasn't fun anymore?
I just can't wrap my head around it.
What's going on?
Wh-What's a helicopter doing at our school?!
Avalon...?
What's with that helicopter?
What's going on? Some sort of incident?
Must be filming for a movie.
What's happening, Sensei?!
Sorry for dropping by without notice.
I was just going to suggest a
practice match against Saki.
A match?
A match against Inui-san!
Will you accept?
Not happening, sorry. It's too sudden.
I'd love to!
Kurashina?
That final was incredible!
You're...
Kurashina Asuka!
Oh, Shindou's opponent in the third round?
Perfect.
Ask for the match, Saki.
Please.
Kurashina.
Y-Yes?
If you start having a hard time,
let Masaya know immediately.
This is a practice match.
Do not push yourself.
O-Okay.
Asuka.
From the second line onwards, go after
her and turn it into a dogfight.
Just stay on the attack.
Got it!
I'm really excited I get to play you.
Sorry, that wasn't appropriate
for pre-match talk.
Here we go!
The All-Japan Summer
Tournament champion, Inui,
and the third-round-loser
but up-and-comer Kurashina!
Their practice match is about to begin!
Who asked for commentary?
Saki, let us show them our beautiful FC.
Okay, Irina.
On your marks...
Set!
It's 1-0.
Inui has opened the scoring.
Saki: Birdcage.
Okay, Irina.
What's this? Inui has come to
a standstill high up above!
I knew it.
She's planning on turning this into a
repeat of the match against Shindou-san!
Kurashina'll have to attack from below,
which will put her at a disadvantage.
That said, if she goes after the next buoy,
Inui will beat her to it.
But at this rate...
Kurashina took a shortcut to the second line,
so she can't go after the next buoy
unless she crosses Inui or touches her!
Coach.
Use a high yo-yo to get directly below Inui!
Directly below?
I'll tell you as soon as she makes a move.
Use an air kick turn to accelerate
in the opposite direction.
That should get you flying close to Inui.
Understood!
Here I go!
There she goes!
Touch her somewhere, anywhere!
Got it!
Here I go!
Once more!
Coach, she keeps fending off all my attacks!
What the...
No matter where she attacks from,
Inui keeps repelling her the same way.
What's going on?
Inui's sending Kurashina flying
downwards at the same angle each time.
That's just a coincidence, right?
Wrong.
It's all been planned precisely.
Asuka...
Create some breathing room!
You'll just wear yourself out like this!
O-Okay!
You're not getting away.
Inui-san...
Kurashina's back is wide open,
so why won't Inui move in for the kill?
How do you like our perfect and beautiful FC?
We took what you left
unfinished and perfected it.
Use some feints, Asuka!
Vary your flight both
vertically and horizontally!
I-I can't!
No matter where I run,
she'll be right above me.
I don't see an exit anywhere!
Thoroughly controlling the opponent
to make them exhaust themselves
by flying around pointlessly...
"Birdcage" is a fitting name for that tactic.
One minute left!
Saki, stay alert and perfect
until the final whistle.
Okay, Irina.
If there's no exit, we'll
have to make one ourselves.
Asuka, use an air kick turn
and fly right into Inui!
From this close, it should
be enough to throw her off!
Asuka!
Asuka?
I was no good at all.
I even got you soaking wet, Misaki-chan.
I'm sorry.
Take a quick shower and change.
And then let's go eat some udon!
Oh, good idea.
B-Back to school we go, then.
Yeah!
R—
Right...
Yeah...
I...
To Be Continued
Preview
I believe this means to just go for it.
That's not it. Let's just eat.
The answer is in the sky!
Episode Nine:
"The Answer is in the Sky!"